<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<root>
  <message id="1">
    <title>Access Denied: Not Administrator</title>
    <body>You are not an administrator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="2">
    <title>Access Denied: Edit Permission Denied</title>
    <body>Either this forum does not exist or you are not allowed to edit.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="3">
    <title>Access Denied: Not Moderator</title>
    <body>You are not a moderator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="4">
    <title>Duplicate Post</title>
    <body>The administrator has configured the forums to not allow duplicate posts.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="5">
    <title>The file you requested cannot be found</title>
    <body>We are sorry, but the file you requested has either been moved or deleted and is no longer available.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="6">
    <title>Not Found: Resource Not Found</title>
    <body>The resource you requested does not exist.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="7">
    <title>User Account Created</title>
    <body>Your user account has been successfully created. You will shortly receive an email containing a temporary password you can use to login.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="8">
    <title>Post Pending Moderation</title>
    <body>You have posted to a forum that requires a moderator to approve posts before they are publicly available. &lt;p /&gt;If the administrator has configured this forum to support email notifications you will receive an email when your post is either approved or denied.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="9">
    <title>Post Not Found</title>
    <body>The post you requested cannot be found or no longer exists. The administrator or moderator may have deleted the post.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="10">
    <title>No Post To Select</title>
    <body>No post could be found for the URL requested.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="11">
    <title>Problem Posting</title>
    <body>We apologize, but there was a problem posting your message. If you continue to experience this, please alert the administrator or moderator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="14">
    <title>User Not Found</title>
    <body>The user you requested cannot be found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="15">
    <title>User Password Changed</title>
    <body>The password has been changed successfully.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="16">
    <title>User Password Change Failed</title>
    <body>An error occurred while attempting to change your password. Please try again.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="17">
    <title>Invalid User Credentials</title>
    <body>The username and/or password cannot be validated or your account has not been approved yet.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="18">
    <title>No Unanswered Posts</title>
    <body>No unanswered posts were found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="19">
    <title>User does not accept Private Messages</title>
    <body>The user you are attempting to send a private message to has turned off private messages.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="20">
    <title>User Search Returned No Results</title>
    <body>Please change your user search criteria as no results were found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="21">
    <title>No Active Posts</title>
    <body>No Active Posts were found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="22">
    <title>Private Messages To Self Not Allowed</title>
    <body>You cannot send private messages to yourself.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="23">
    <title>Your account is pending approval</title>
    <body>Until your account is approved you will be unable to sign in. You will receive an email when your account has been approved.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="24">
    <title>Welcome!</title>
    <body>Your account has been created and you are signed in. Congratulations! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You're now ready to meet like-minded community members and start participating in valuable conversations.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="25">
    <title>Account Not Approved</title>
    <body>You have not been approved to access this community.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="26">
    <title>Account Banned</title>
    <body>You are not allowed to access this community.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="27">
    <title>Unknown Login Error</title>
    <body>We apologize, but an unknown error occurred while attempting to verify your credentials. Please try again.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="28">
    <title>Unable to Send Email</title>
    <body>We apologize, but an error occurred while attempting to send email.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="29">
    <title>New User Registration Disabled</title>
    <body>The administrator has disabled new account creation. Please check back later - or email the administrator - to see if it is possible to register.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="30">
    <title>Login Disabled</title>
    <body>The administrator has globally disabled login. Please check back later - or email the administrator - to see if it is possible to login.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="31">
    <title>Access Denied</title>
    <body>You do not have permissions to perform the requested action.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="32">
    <title>Access Denied: Post Permission Denied</title>
    <body>Either this forum does not exist or you are not allowed to post.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="33">
    <title>${group_propercase} Not Found</title>
    <body>The requested ${group_propercase} cannot be found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="34">
    <title>Email template not found</title>
    <body>The requested email template cannot be found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="35">
    <title>Search Unknown Error</title>
    <body>We apologize, but an unknown error has occurred during search. Please try your search again.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="36">
    <title>Access Denied: Reply Permission Denied</title>
    <body>Either the forum does not exist or you do not have permissions to reply to posts within the forum.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="37">
    <title>Access Denied: Announce Permission Denied</title>
    <body>Either the forum does not exist or you do not have permissions to create announcements within the forum.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="38">
    <title>Permission Expired: Post Edit Permission Expired</title>
    <body>The administrator has configured this forum to have a time limit for editing messages. If you still require a message to be edited, please check with a forum moderator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="39">
    <title>Post Locked</title>
    <body>This post is locked and does not allow replies.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="40">
    <title>Permission Expired: Post Delete Permission Expired</title>
    <body>The administrator has configured this forum to have a time limit for deleting messages. If you still require a message to be deleted, please check with a forum moderator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="41">
    <title>Access Denied: Delete Permission Denied</title>
    <body>Either the forum does not exist or you do not have permission to delete posts within the forum.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="43">
	<title>Skin Not Found</title>
	<body>Skin file not found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="45">
    <title>No Results Found</title>
    <body>There were no search results found.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="46">
	<title>Attachment not Allowed</title>
	<body>Your post has been saved, but the attachment was not.&lt;p/&gt;The administrator has denied uploads of certain file types and the file must have only one extension (filename.ext).</body>
  </message>

  <message id="47">
	<title>Access Denied</title>
	<body>You do not have permission to view/download this item.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="48">
	<title>Email sent to user</title>
	<body>The email was sent to the user.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="49">
	<title>Attachment Too Large</title>
	<body>Your post has been saved, but the attachment was not.&lt;p/&gt;Your attachment exceeded the maximum size limit.&lt;p/&gt;While your post was submitted, if it was made to a moderated forum it will not be available until approved by a moderator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="50">
	<title>Attachments Disabled</title>
	<body>Your post has been saved, but the attachment was not.&lt;p/&gt;Attachments have been disabled by the forums administrator.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="51">
	<title>Secret Answer Changed</title>
	<body>Your old secret answer has been successfully changed. Use it whenever it is required to recover your password.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="52">
	<title>Secret Answer Change Failed</title>
	<body>An error occurred while attempting to change your secret answer. Please try again.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="53">
    <title>Role Not Found</title>
    <body>The role you requested cannot be found.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="54">
    <title>Role Updated</title>
    <body>Role details has been updated.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="55">
    <title>Role Deleted</title>
    <body>Role has been deleted.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="56">
    <title>Role Operation Not Permitted</title>
    <body>You could not perform the action you've just tried on selected role.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="57">
    <title>Resource not found</title>
    <body>The resource you requested does not exist.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="65">
    <title>Access Denied: Post Flood Prevention</title>
    <body>The required time between posts has not been met.  Please wait a few seconds and try to post again.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="67">
    <title>Access Denied: Delete Permission Denied</title>
    <body>Permission to delete the post has been denied.  A post cannot be deleted if replies have been made to it.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="68">
    <title>No Unread Posts</title>
    <body>No posts were found that you have not read.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="69">
    <title>User Password Reset</title>
    <body>You have requested that a new password be generated and sent to your email address (&lt;font color="red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;{0}&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;). Please allow up to 15 minutes for it to take effect.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="72">
    <title>User Password Link Sent</title>
    <body>You have requested a link be sent to your email address (&lt;font color="red"&gt;&lt;b&gt;{0}&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;) which will enable you to reset your password. The email will arrive shortly.</body>
  </message>  

  <message id="73">
    <title>User Already Logged In</title>
    <body>You are already logged in. If you were redirected here while trying to access another part of the site, please contact the administrator to request additional permissions.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="74">
    <title>Deactivated User Account</title>
    <body>The user you have selected to view or contact has been deactivated by the administrator.</body>
  </message>  
  
  <message id="75">
    <title>Invalid License</title>
    <body>This site does not have an adequate license to complete the requested action. Please contact the administrator.</body>
  </message> 

  <message id="76">
    <title>License Error</title>
    <body>An error occurred while attempting to load currently installed licenses.  Please contact the administrator.</body>
  </message> 
  
  <message id="77">
	<title>Invitation is Missing or Invalid</title>
	<body>New users are allowed to be created by invitation only.  The invitation key was missing or is currently invalid.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="78">
    <title>Invitation Accepted</title>
    <body>You have successfully accepted the invitation to join this community.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="79">
    <title>Welcome!</title>
    <body>You have successfully accepted the invitation to join this community.  Your account has been created and you are now signed in.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="80">
	<title>Duplicate Tag</title>
	<body>A tag with the name specified already exists.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="81">
	<title>Blog File Quota Exceeded</title>
	<body>The blog file storage total file size quota has been exceeded. Please try uploading a smaller file, or contact the site administrator to adjust the quota settings.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="82">
	<title>File Type Not Valid</title>
	<body>This type of file is not allowed.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="83">
	<title>Blog File Storage Not Allowed</title>
	<body>Blog File Storage is disabled.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="84">
    <title>Site File Quota Exceeded</title>
    <body>The site file storage total file size quota has been exceeded.  Please try uploading a smaller file, or contact the site administrator to adjust the quota settings.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="85">
    <title>File Storage Not Allowed</title>
    <body>File storage is not currently allowed on this site.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="86">
    <title>User File Quota Exceeded</title>
    <body>Your file storage total file size quota has been exceeded.  Please try uploading a smaller file, or contact the site administrator to adjust the quota settings.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="87">
    <title>User Storage Not Allowed</title>
    <body>User file storage is not currently allowed on this site.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="88">
    <title>Duplicate Page Keys Not Allowed</title>
	<body>A page by this name exists in this wiki already. Please choose another name for this page.</body>
  </message>

	<message id="90">
		<title>Forums Temporarily Disabled</title>
		<body>The administrator has temporarily disabled the forums.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="91">
		<title>${groups_propercase} Temporarily Disabled</title>
		<body>The administrator has temporarily disabled the ${groups_lowercase}.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="92">
		<title>Media Galleries Temporarily Disabled</title>
		<body>The administrator has temporarily disabled the media galleries.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="93">
		<title>Blogs Temporarily Disabled</title>
		<body>The administrator has temporarily disabled the blogs.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="94">
		<title>Wikis Temporarily Disabled</title>
		<body>The administrator has temporarily disabled the wikis.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="95">
		<title>Default Wiki Page is Locked</title>
		<body>The default page for a wiki can not be deleted. Please edit the content to be blank instead.</body>
	</message>

  <message id="96">
    <title>Maximum Upload Size Exceeded</title>
    <body>The file was uploaded that was too large.  Please upload a smaller file or contact your administrator to adjust allowed file size settings.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="97">
    <title>Unknown Request Error</title>
    <body>
        <![CDATA[
      Your request could not be processed.  This error can occur if:
      <ol>
      <li>A file was uploaded that was too large</li>
      <li>The request was taking too long to process</li>
      <li>The request was formatted improperly</li>
      <li>An unexpected error occurred on the server</li>
      </ol>
    ]]>
      </body>
  </message>

	<message id="98">
		<title>Duplicate Field Group Name</title>
		<body>The Field Group name must be unique.</body>
	</message>


    <message id="99">
        <title>Over Licensed Settings</title>
        <body>
            This installation of Zimbra Social is over its licensed settings, so your last request
            could not be fulfilled.  Please contact your system administrator.
        </body>
    </message>

    <message id="100">
        <title>Over Licensed Settings</title>
        <body>
            This installation of Zimbra Social is over its licensed settings, so your last request
            could not be fulfilled.  Please contact your system administrator.
        </body>
    </message>

  <message id="101">
    <title>Membership Pending</title>
    <body>
        Access to this group is pending the acceptance of your membership request.  Please check back later.      
    </body>
  </message>

  <message id="103">
    <title>Mute Successful</title>
    <body>
      You will no longer receive e-mail notifications from this thread.
    </body>
  </message>

  <message id="104">
    <title>Page Not Found</title>
    <body>The page you requested cannot be found or no longer exists. The administrator or moderator may have deleted the page.</body>
  </message>
  
  <message id="105">
    <title>Validation Error</title>
    <body>An error occurred validating a field.  Please go to the previous page and try again.</body>
  </message>

	<message id="106">
		<title>System Account</title>
		<body>The user account you are trying to use is a built-in system account that can not be logged in or interacted with.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="107">
		<title>Filename Too Long</title>
		<body>The filename attempting to be uploaded is too long, try a shorter filename.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="108">
		<title>Unable to Upload</title>
		<body>The file is unable to be uploaded at this time, please try again later. If the problem persists, contact the site administrator.</body>
	</message>

    <message id="110">
        <title>Account Locked</title>
        <body>Your account has been locked for exceeding the number of incorrect login attempts.  Please try again later or contact the site administrator.</body>
    </message>

	<message id="111">
		<title>OAuth Request failure</title>
		<body>A connection was unable to be made with the authentication server or a bad request was made, please try again later. If the problem persists, contact the site administrator.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="112">
		<title>OAuth Error</title>
		<body>An error occurred while trying to validate the login, please try again later. If the problem persists, contact the site administrator.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="113">
		<title>Email Template Parsing Error</title>
		<body>An error occurred while trying to parse an email template.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="114">
		<title>Content Fragment Rendering Error</title>
		<body>An error occurred while trying to render the content fragment.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="115">
		<title>Post Comment too long</title>
		<body>The comment you tried to add is too long.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="117">
		<title>Registration is unavailable</title>
		<body>This site is not accepting new user registrations at this time.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="119">
		<title>OAuth Login Failed</title>
		<body>Login failed, please try again. If the problem persists, contact the site administrator.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="120">
		<title>Comments not supported for specified content type.</title>
		<body>The content you tried to comment on does not support comments.</body>
	</message>

	<message id="121">
		<title>Ratings not supported for specified content type.</title>
		<body>The content you tried to rate does not support ratings.</body>
	</message>

  <message id="123">
    <title>Licensing Restriction</title>
    <body>The action you performed is not allowed with the installed license.</body>
  </message>

	<message id="125">
		<title>User Account Not Created</title>
		<body>User account has not been successfully created.</body>
	</message>

    <message id="126">
        <title>OAuth Client Application Authorization Not Allowed</title>
        <body>This client doesn't have the grant type allowed to perform this type of authorization.</body>
    </message>

	<message id="127">
		<title>Duplicate Post</title>
		<body>The administrator has configured the media gallery to not allow duplicate posts.</body>
	</message>

    <message id="129">
        <title>Administrator Login Disabled from IP</title>
        <body>You are unable to login to an administrator account from your IP address.</body>
    </message>

  <message id="130">
    <title>Page not Found</title>
    <body>The requested page is not a part of the current theme.</body>
  </message>

	<message id="132">
		<title>Site Not Active</title>
		<body>This site is not currently active, please try again later or contact the site administrator.</body>
	</message>

  <message id="133">
    <title>Mailing List already exists</title>
    <body>The requested mailing list is already in use.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="134">
    <title>Unable to process email</title>
    <body>The email could not be processed.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="135">
    <title>CSS Rendering Error</title>
    <body>There was an error rendering the CSS file.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="136">
    <title>System Account not found</title> 
    <body>The built-in anonymous or service user accounts have not been found.</body> 
  </message>

  <message id="138">
    <title>Embeddable Content Fragment Error</title>
    <body>There was a error with an embedded content fragment.</body>
  </message>

  <message id="999">
    <title>Unknown Error</title>
    <body>We apologize, but an unknown error has occurred in the forums. &lt;p/&gt;This error has been logged.</body>
  </message>

</root>